helpteaching.com 2017-05-19

# Privacy Policy - HelpTeaching.com

The following is Help Teaching's policy on collecting certain personal information about you. 

## IP Address

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We do not use your IP address to gather demographic information. 

## Cookies

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your member session. We use cookies to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

## Registration

Our site's registration form requires members to give us a member name and e-mail address. The member's e-mail address is used to contact the member when necessary. Members may opt-out of receiving future mailings by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of such mailings. 

## Help Teaching Pro

Help Teaching Pro requires a paid subscription. Help Teaching may contact subscribers regarding the status of their subscriptions. Help Teaching does not store billing information on its system. Payment is processed through PayPal. For more information please refer to [PayPal's Privacy Policy](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside). 

## The Organization Collecting the Information

The data that you provide for Help Teaching is collected from the www.helpteaching.com Web site by SureSwift Worldwide. 

## With Whom May the Information Be Shared

In order to grow our site, we may form relationships with partners to promote Help Teaching and encourage new members to join. One form of these relationships, but not limited to this form, is a co-branded Web site which combines the partner's look-and-feel with our topic areas and content. These co-branded pages allow us to keep the member information and content hosted on our secure servers. Each new member must accept our terms and conditions, including this privacy statement. Because some partners are helping us grow by promoting the Help Teaching name and co-branded page, we sometimes share information about the members that sign up through the partner's co-branded page. In all cases, our partners commit to honoring our privacy policy. This site may from time-to-time contain links to other sites. Help Teaching is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

## Invite a Friend

If a member elects to use our referral service for informing a friend of our site, we ask them for their friend's name and e-mail address. Help Teaching will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the site. Help Teaching does not store these e-mail addresses and names. 

## How You Can Correct Any Inaccuracies in the Information

This site gives members the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. You may change the information in "My Questions", "My Groups" and "My Tests" at any time by logging in to the site. You may change your password and e-mail address in the account module. 

## Notification of Change

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the Web site. We will post these changes so that you will always know what information we gather, how we may use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check this site for information about revisions to our privacy policy. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us. 

_This policy was last modified on July 27, 2013_
